[{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Stagecoach owned South West Trains before losing the rights to FirstGroup and MTR in March of 2017", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Geography", "question": "Only one country in the world starts with the letter Q", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Vehicles", "question": "The term GTO was originated by Ferrari", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Geography", "question": "Switzerland has four national languages English being one of them", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Politics", "question": "Nazi Germany surrendered on Harry Truman039s birthday while he was president", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Mathematics", "question": "In Topology the complement of an open set is a closed set", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "The character Plum from No Game No Life is a girl", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Danganronpa 2 Goodbye Despair featured all of the surviving students from the first game", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "History", "question": "During the Winter War the amount of Soviet Union soliders that died or went missing was five times more than Finland039s", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "History", "question": "Joseph Stalin039s real name was Ioseb Bessarionis dze Dzugashvili", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Film", "question": "The weapon Clint Eastwood uses in Dirty Harry was a 44 Automag", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "History", "question": "The Kingdom of Prussia briefly held land in Estonia", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Computers", "question": "The IBM PC used an Intel 8008 microprocessor clocked at 477 MHz and 8 kilobytes of memory", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Mathematics", "question": "L039Hpital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Art", "question": "The Statue of Liberty039s official name is Liberty Enlightening the World", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Spoon theory is a theory utilizing Spoons as a metaphor for energy they can use in a day", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Throughout the entirety of Dragon Ball Z Goku only kills two characters a miniboss named Yakon and Kid Buu", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In Undertale having a Fun Value set to 5657 will play the Wrong Number Song Call", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the To LoveRu series Peke is considered a female robot", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Celebrities", "question": "Lady Gaga039s real name is Stefani Joanne Angelina Germanotta", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Politics", "question": "Joko Widodo has appeared in the cover of a TIME magazine", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Computers", "question": "DHCP stands for Dynamic Host Configuration Port", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Comics", "question": "In the comic book Archie Betty is friends with Veronica because she is rich", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In The Witcher 3 the Zoltan Chivay Gwent card can be found under the Hanged Man039s Tree", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Mathematics", "question": "If you could fold a piece of paper in half 50 times its039 thickness will be 34th the distance from the Earth to the Sun", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In the game Melty Blood Actress Again Current Code you can enter Blood Heat mode in Half Moon style", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Books", "question": "Harry Potter was born on July 31st 1980", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In Portal 2 Cave Johnson started out Aperture Science as a shower curtain company", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Music", "question": "The song Mystery Train was released by artist Little Junior039s Blue Flames in 1953", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The first Metal Gear game was released for the PlayStation 1", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "TF2 Sentry rocket damage falloff is calculated based on the distance between the sentry and the enemy not the engineer and the enemy", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The video game Fuel has an open world that is 5560 square miles", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Music", "question": "The band STRFKR was also briefly known as Pyramiddd", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Mythology", "question": "Rannamaari was a sea demon that haunted the people of the Maldives and had to be appeased monthly with the sacrifice of a virgin girl", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "History", "question": "The Battle of Trafalgar took place on October 23rd 1805", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Film", "question": "Cube Cube 2 Hypercube and Cube Zero were directed by the same person", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Music", "question": "The song Scatman039s World was released after Scatman SkiBaBopBaDopBop", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In Call Of Duty World At War the first appearance of the PPSH41 in Zombies was in the map Der Riese", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In Minecraft gold tools are faster than diamond tools", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Mythology", "question": "Janus was the Roman god of doorways and passageways", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Unturned originally started as a Roblox game", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the Kagerou Daze series Shintaro Kisaragi is prominently shown with the color red", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Computers", "question": "The TMobile Sidekick smartphone is a rebranded version of the Danger Hiptop", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Mathematics", "question": "The binary number 101001101 is equivalent to the Decimal number 334", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "NCIS stands for Navy Corps Investigative Service", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Television", "question": "The Klingon home planet is Qo039noS", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "In Scandinavian languages the letter means river", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Vehicles", "question": "In 1993 Swedish car manufacturer Saab experimented with replacing the steering wheel with a joystick in a Saab 9000", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Number 16 Bus Shelter was a child039s name that was approved by the New Zealand government", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Politics", "question": "George Clinton Vice President of the United States 18051812 is an ancestor of President Bill Clinton", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]